# VOLODYMYR VYSOTSKYI



### Contacts

- ogithub.com/qnightmare
- in v-vysotskyi
- ⋈ qnightmare@ukr.net
- **\( +38 095 473 2220**

# Languages

Ukrainian

English

### Summary

A conscientious and ambitious graduate of the Faculty of Electronics, Ivan Franko National University of Lviv. I have an analytical staff capable of self-study. I have experience in working with clients and personnel management. I know PC hardware and peripherals

### Skills

HTML CSS Java Script GIT React

# Experience

Student at cource Eleks bootcamp HTML/CSS/JS march 2022 - may 2022

Job Responsibilities: Become a front end developer

System administrator at Phoenix-Plus company august 2009 - present

Job Responsibilities: LAN, WAN support, server support, user support. Operation, maintenance and repair of office equipment, printing machines, personal computers

Leading electronics at Lviv Regional Hydrometeorology Center

march 2008 september 2008

Job Responsibilities: Ensuring the operation of the local network, telegraph, telephone, Setting up a satellite weather monitoring system. Ensuring autonomous operation of equipment 24/7

# Education

Master of Electronics: Physical and biomedical electronics. 2003 - 2008

Ivan Franko National University of Lviv, Ukraine